Guide to the Administrative Guide
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Administrative guide
1961-1996
SC4-1101
Stanford University
6 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Associated Materials
https://adminguide.stanford.edu/
Arrangement note
Arranged chronologically.
Access Terms
Stanford University--Administration.; Universities and colleges--Administration.
Collection Contents
- Contents
  - Table of contents, 1967-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Prefatory material, 1968-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Indexes, 1967-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sections 11-19 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sections 20-22.5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Sections 22.6-22.11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sections 23.1-27 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Sections 28.1-28.7 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sections 30-35.3 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Sections 35.4-36.8 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Sections 41-54 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Sections 55-73 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sections 74- (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1961 Jan - 1966 Dec (Box 4)
  - 1967 Jan - 1969 Dec (Box 5)
  - 1970 Jan - 1979 Dec (Box 6)
  - 1980 Jan - 1996 Mar (Box 7)